Boss!
One bowl of tofu pudding, please.
Fenghua, why are you back?
Auntie.
We'd like a bowl too.
Wanghe, Xingchi, Haikuo!
How did you all get back?
By car.
It must have been a tiring journey.
Hurry, hurry.
Go home first.
Let your family know you're back.
Come back to my shop for tofu pudding later.
Are we closing?
At least for now.
This is great!
Are you back for the Mid-Autumn Festival?
I missed you.
This is wonderful!
Eat up quickly.
This...
Look at you.
Coming all this way just to visit.
You're really something.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I wanted to come back for a family reunion dinner.
You're busy,
and we can video chat now.
It's the same wherever you are.
Exactly.
How about I go back to Beijing now?
Don't you dare.
Here.
Have some buns.
Come.
Okay.
It's hot.
How long are you staying this time?
I have to leave tomorrow.
Leaving tomorrow?
What’s the point of making this trip back here?
Work's been hectic.
This time, it was Wanghe who helped arrange time off too.
Otherwise, I couldn't have come.
It's good to be busy.
Being busy...
means the company values you more.
They're willing to give you more responsibilities.
Grandpa, Wanghe is now my boss.
Xingchi and I work under him.
Right, this boss of yours...
How is he treating you?
Pretty good.
He’s been a big help to the two of us at work.
We can learn a lot from him.
What about his personal life?
Their personal lives aren’t as good as mine.
They're both single.
They need to learn from me in this aspect.
These days, your grandson also has
someone to come home to after work.
Dad, did you hear that?
Your grandson
is shamelessly bragging and showing off.
It's better to be like you.
As a single, you're free.
Cut it out.
Alright, I'm done talking.
I'll go prepare some food for you.
Ask them if there's anything they want to eat.
Okay, thanks, Dad.
Don't be like your dad.
Oh yes, Grandpa.
My girlfriend bought you some mooncakes.
Really?
They're from Daoxiangcun.
That's nice.
I'm off to work.
Our son just got back.
Why can't you have a chat with him and go later?
It's not like he doesn't have a phone.
Can't we chat on the phone?
It's fine, just go ahead.
I'm off then.
Come home early after work.
Where else could I go?
Do you two still argue these days?
What arguments?
We're too old for that now.
Just thinking about it is exhausting.
Don't worry, everything's fine.
Don't just share the good news and leave out the bad.
You're the one who only shares good news.
With all that you've experienced in Beijing,
you nearly gave me a heart attack.
You know that?
Mom.
Your son is on the right path now.
Let me tell you.
In just two years,
all the things I bragged about before
will be fulfilled.
There's never enough money to be made.
As long as you stay on the right path,
your mom will be at peace.
I know.
Have an egg.
Granny Ma.
Fenghua has come back from Beijing.
She's here to see you.
How quickly time flies.
In the blink of an eye,
it's been 7 years since Granny Ma passed away.
The same goes for Siyi.
She still hasn't contacted you?
That ungrateful girl.
I wonder if she’s doing well
on her own out there.
You'd think at least during the holidays,
she'd send a greeting.
All that worry for nothing.
She must have her reasons.
If she has her reasons, she should say so.
You were such close friends,
yet she left without a word.
Even the closest relationships
can't withstand such torment.
I believe that
one day,
when she's worn out from wandering around,
she'll come back.
Who knows if we'll still be around by then.
By the time she returns,
this courtyard might...
already be emptied.
Fenghua, Auntie.
My dad's treating everyone to lunch, so please come.
Alright.
I want to eat soft-braised eel,
braised shredded tofu...
Granny Ma,
it's Mid-Autumn Festival.
We're all together now.
Squirrel-shaped mandarin fish.
Here it comes!
Grandpa, don't drink too much.
Okay, I don't need you to tell me.
By the way, come back often.
Come back and visit us often.
Come back often.
But...
He has a lot of business in Beijing.
Welcome, Mayor.
Happy holidays.
Cheers!
Today...
There's more good news.
The comprehensive upgrading and renovation of our Flower Street
has already begun.
Upgrade? To what?
It's exactly this courtyard
where we are all living now.
Houses that have fallen into disrepair will,
in principle, be renovated on-site.
On-site?
Then, then...
Do we need to move out?
Currently, the plan
has been submitted.
Let's try to make plans
and minimise disruption to your daily lives.
That's great!
When will it start?
If everything goes as planned,
next month.
That's so soon!
That is really quick and productive!
Indeed!
This is great news that deserves celebration.
Renovation...
What will it be like after the renovation?
I don't know, they're still planning.
But they'll most likely
try to preserve the original appearance of the old buildings as much as possible.
Does our courtyard count as an old building?
It should be.
My grandpa said
the main hall is over 200 years old.
As for Granny Ma's residence,
county records say it once produced a successful imperial examination candidate.
What about my house?
It produced servants.
No, for real though.
Granny Ma lives in the main hall,
so that's the master's room.
Your house and mine are the peripheral rooms,
where the maids and servants lived.
No wonder my grades were poor when I was young.
So it’s an issue of feng shui.
If I had lived in the same room as Siyi back then,
I might have gotten into a 985 university.
I think even if Siyi had been admitted, she might not have gone.
I remember she told me before the college entrance exam
that she thinks experience from traveling is more valuable than reading countless books.
And over these years,
she's been proving this saying with her actions.
You knew Siyi would leave?
I guessed that it was a possibility.
Why didn't you tell us back then?
With Siyi's personality,
what good would it have done to say anything?
Could we have kept her from leaving?
I used to worry a lot about Siyi too.
I was worried she'd suffer out there alone,
or be mistreated.
But I don't think so anymore.
Just recently,
together with Grandpa Zhou, Uncle Shao, and my dad,
we went on a business trip.
It was to trace the Shao family's ancestral footsteps.
It wasn't really that far,
but along the way,
I felt so happy
and excited.
I felt that it was the first time I truly
experienced the joy of traveling.
I believe it's the same for Siyi.
As long as you have hope
and a goal,
when you are on the road,
no matter how tired or difficult it gets for you,
you'll feel that
your heart is beating,
and life has its purpose.
Come on.
A toast
to Siyi, who's far away.
To Siyi.
I'm fine.
Sit down, sit down.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Alright.
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival!
Fenghua.
Here,
have a tangerine.
The new ones are really sweet.
Thanks, Mom.
Stop watching.
Chat with me for a bit.
Every time we talk on the phone, you're always in such a rush.
You hang up before we're even done talking.
Well, go ahead.
Be honest with me.
Do you have a boyfriend?
What do you mean 'ah'?
I'm your mother.
Your eyes can't fool me.
What's wrong with my eyes?
They are pretty normal.
Come on, tell me.
There's no one, really.
I'm so busy I barely have time to eat,
let alone find a boyfriend.
So you plan to stay single forever?
Well, I can't force it if there's no one.
I'm not the type to simply settle.
Well, your dad and I just settled for each other.
Aren't we doing fine now?
Fine.
I'll just find someone randomly then.
Don't be picky when the time comes,
complaining about this and that.
That won't do.
Character comes first.
I don't care about anything else.
Well, rest assured,
he has pretty good character.
Looks like you’re busted!
So, do you have a boyfriend?
Do you have a boyfriend?
You tricked me!
Come clean with me. What does he do?
How old is he?
Do you have any photos?
Hurry.
Let me see!
Mom! Mom!
I haven't decided if I want to be with him yet.
Don't pressure me.
Why haven't you decided?
It's complicated.
I'm really looking forward to it,
but I also feel scared.
Give me some time.
When I've figured it out,
I'll tell you right away.
I promise.
What else are you waiting for?
Worrying about this and that.
By the time you figure it out,
it'll be too late.
It won't be.
Why not?
What era are we living in?
Who's going to wait for you?
If you have feelings, just go for it.
You have to capture the opportunity.
If you don't, they'll turn around and find someone else.
How does that song lyric go?
"I've been waiting for you until my heart aches,
been waiting for you until I'm gone."
They'll be long gone.
You silly child.
Seriously.
Wait and wait.
Here, Son. This one has roe in it.
Eat more.
Just come back when you crave for it.
Tell me.
How much money have you saved?
You mean savings?
Any kind of money.
We just want to know how much money you have.
This way, we'll know how much money we need to give you
when you get married.
Right?
Why should you give me money?
How can I ask you guys for money when it's my wedding?
Say no more.
Just tell us the truth.
How much money
do you really have?
I don't have much cash.
About 70,000 to 80,000 yuan.
I used the rest of my money to buy stocks.
Which stock did you buy?
Moutai.
And I have a car.
It's gifted by my boss.
That's not much.
Wait.
So...
all these years you've been out there,
what have you been up to?
Look at you.
Pretending
to be a successful person around us?
I have options in Bee.
Quite a lot of them, actually.
Once the company gets listed,
I'll have complete financial independence.
What if it doesn't get listed?
We could do a merger and acquisition.
As long as this company doesn't go bankrupt,
I won't be poor.
So you mean...
you're really a successful businessman?
How could I fake that, Mom?
Look at our son.
He's so smart.
He's not the kind to be taken advantage of.
Son, have you ever thought about
coming back to develop your career here?
Come back?
What for?
You see, Mayor Gu said
that
once our canal makes it onto the World Heritage List,
the development potential for Flower Street will be huge.
You're a successful entrepreneur now.
A successful businessman.
I don't consider it an accomplishment if you enjoy success alone.
If you are really capable,
come back and lead everyone to make a fortune.
As the advertisement goes,
"It's only beneficial when it delivers for everyone."
Think about it.
It's because you two miss me, right?
You can come to Beijing.
Why should we go to Beijing?
To live with me.
Live?
I'm not used to living in Beijing.
I'm used to it.
Come on.
Come on, Mom.
T-The wine is finished.
All you know is drink.
Go buy me another pot.
I want one that has been aged 8 years.
You've been drinking every day.
I'll go.
Do you know which shop it is?
Of course. How can I forget?
Tell him
it's me who's buying, and keep it on my tab.
What do you think?
I won't go to Beijing.
I know you can't leave the canal.
Did you notice
there's something different about him this time?
What's different?
Aren't you afraid of falling down?
It's okay. I can swim.
You didn't go home for dinner?
I did. What about you?
I came out to buy wine for my dad.
Are you feeling down?
No.
Then why are you sitting here?
People might think
you want to jump into the river.
In Beijing,
I always feel like I'm a passerby.
I always feel restrained.
But when I'm home,
I feel empowered.
I feel like I'm not afraid of anything.
There's nothing I wouldn't say
and nothing that I wouldn't do.
Tell me about it then.
Xie Wanghe.
Do you have a crush on me?
Since when?
Does it matter?
Yes, very.
Let me think.
Yesterday?
I can't remember
when it was exactly.
Which year?
Before we went to Beijing
or after?
After.
In my third year of college,
I was working on a travel marketing project with others.
But they all skipped town.
We lost all our money.
Stop drinking.
Go home.
Fenghua.
Give it to me!
Drink with me.
You, stop drinking!
Just have a drink with me.
Why are you drinking?
Go home now!
Take your glasses.
Stop drinking!
Go home!
It's none of your business!
Entrepreneurship
is never smooth sailing.
If you fail, just learn from the lesson.
Then why is it me who fails every time?
Why?
If I only failed once, you could say it's bad luck.
But I failed twice, and then three times.
I've failed every time.
I'm just a huge joke!
When I was little, who's the one that told me
we should get up
from wherever we fell?
Even if you can't pick yourself up,
I'm here with you.
As long as you still want to win,
and you still have that will,
you won't fail
in the future.
Just because of that?
Your motivational words
didn't do much for me.
Those two slaps were what
knocked some sense into me.
Are you a masochist?
You just knew?
I should be even harsher to you in the future.
This way,
you'll like me more.
So, do you like me?
This atmosphere.
Did you have this all planned...
Thank you.
For what?
For not avoiding.
I'm on a bridge.
Where can I hide?
Jump into the river?
No.
It wasn't fair for me.
What do you want then?
We're even now.
So...
are we boyfriend and girlfriend now?
We've kissed.
How could we not be?
Let's not tell anyone yet.
Let's keep it a secret for now.
Why?
It was too sudden.
I've got a lot on my mind.
Okay.
Go back and think about it.
Just don't regret it when you wake up tomorrow.
It's possible.
Good night.
Why are you still up?
Mom.
Has Dad
liked anyone else before?
How dare he?
I mean before.
Before you knew each other.
What does that have to do with me?
As long as he promised
he'd only love me from now on.
So,
you think it's okay even if
he has someone else in his heart?
I don't care who he has in his heart.
As long as he's by my side,
and I have his money in my pocket.
As for the rest, I can't care less.
I’ll just think of him as having an idol.
You're so open-minded.
Actually,
as the old saying goes,
"Soft fire makes sweet malt."
In life,
there are things that you will never understand.
And you'll hesitate
about what choice you should make.
So, you may as well not think about anything
or do anything.
Just let it be?
If you don't do anything, nothing will go wrong.
Don't worry.
Give it time.
Time will take care of everything for you.
Good girl, go to sleep.
You'll have a day on the road tomorrow.
Here.
Mom, stop.
Stop putting more stuff in. There's not enough room.
Take it.
I still have to take two people in the backseats.
I'll put the water here.
And there's fruit too.
Take this back.
No one wants mooncakes.
You must take it.
This is...
I can buy everything in Beijing.
I know you can buy everything there,
but nothing is better than what you get from home.
Don't work so hard, you know?
Be careful, be careful.
I'll just load them up.
Wanghe.
Keep an eye on her.
Okay.
Make sure she eats on time and doesn't stay up late.
I'll keep a close eye on her every day.
Okay.
Every day?
I don't have time every day.
Well, at least call me once a week.
All right, I will.
I heard you.
It’d be best if you could bring
someone home for Mom next time.
Haikuo!
Xingchi!
Hurry up, hurry up.
Coming.
I'll try.
Go.
Give me that bag.
Dad.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
Who are you decocting the medicine for?
Who is sick?
When are you leaving tomorrow?
In the morning.
Hey. I'm asking you.
Who is sick?
Your grandpa.
Grandpa?
Yes.
What's wrong with him?
He has Alzheimer's disease.
I didn't tell you
because I didn't want you to be worried.
It's not as serious as you think.
It's common for people to get
this disease with age.
Does Grandpa know?
Of course not.
I won't leave tomorrow.
Just leave tomorrow as planned.
Get back to work.
I'm here.
By the way,
don't tell anyone else.
What's wrong?
How much did you drink last night?
Why are you so quiet?
I'm tired.
Put on some music.
Okay.
Next,
your sweetheart from Flower Street
will sing you the song,
"Just Like You".
Ready, go.
♫I'm just like you♫
♫Strong like you♫
♫Trying my best to pursue my dream like you♫
Friends in the back, come on.
♫Even if I get hurt, even if there are ups and downs♫
♫Only after the storm will there be a charming fragrance♫
I think you should
redesign the homepage.
Retake photos of the dishes.
For food delivery,
presentation is just as important as taste.
Fine, I'll do as you say.
Alright, I'll be on my way.
Okay.
Have a seat.
No need, no need.
Be careful.
Go get busy.
Sure, sure.
Come, have some water.
Hurry.
Here, take this.
This is for you.
Be careful next time, okay?
Grandpa.
Let me carry that for you.
Okay.
Let me take a photo for you,
alright?
I used to make more than 8,000 yuan a month.
But this month, I only made a bit over 6,000 yuan.
I made more than 7,000 yuan last month,
but only 3,000 yuan this month.
Hello, Chief.
Let’s have a meeting.
What is Xingchi trying to do?
Why is he only letting us take on 30 orders?
He said it's for our own good
as he didn't want us to be tired.
Isn't that crazy?
Are we here to do nothing?
Put it here.
Careful.
Hold on a second.
I need some water.
Let me help you.
Be careful.
And this.
This year is a year full of challenges.
Facing fierce market competition,
the group's courier business has reached a new high.
Annual business volume has reached approximately 3 billion yuan,
with sorting efficiency improving by 17%.
We have further increased our market share,
and in turn, strengthening our leading position in this industry.
Could it not have been?
Everyone's exhausted.
If you ask me,
they shouldn't have invited
those celebrities for this celebratory gala.
They should invite us couriers.
Right, right.
We should get Fenghua to go.
You should totally go.
Look at how pretty you are.
What can I do?
Fenghua looks great.
Fenghua, you should represent us couriers up there.
Stop kidding.
Let's keep working hard.
That day will come.
This year,
we've fought a good battle.
Next year,
we'll let the whole of Haidian know
which station is the most reliable.
Do you have confidence?
No.
No?
-Yes.
-Yes!
Fenghua.
They're just teasing you.
Then let's eat well and keep working.
Okay!
Let's eat, let's eat.
Fenghua, I'll go get you a bowl of soup.
Thank you, Auntie.
What are you doing?
Want some supper?
Let's spend New Year’s Eve together next week?
Permission granted. You may leave now.
You little brat, you really think you're Concubine Hua now?
Cheers to the last day of this year.
Isn't Xiaohui coming?
She's working overtime.
She has a lot of work to do.
She's so busy, she doesn't even have time to come home.
Did you two fight again?
No.
She’s holding onto my payroll card.
She can spend my money however she wants.
Look at my attitude.
What can she buy with your salary?
It's all about the attitude.
You're single. What do you know?
That's right.
Attitude is the key.
What girls care about the most is undivided love.
Even if I'm the most ordinary girl in the world,
you can only like me.
Yes.
This is how it works in Korean dramas.
You still have time to watch Korean dramas?
We are so busy that we don't even have time to eat.
Hey.
Can't I have some spare time?
203's performance...
I know it's unsatisfactory.
Don't worry.
I've got an idea.
Things will change drastically after the New Year.
I'm worried that you'll be eliminated
before that change happens.
Are you here to pick a fight today?
Bro.
Your performance is not good.
Can't I say something about it?
If your performance was better,
would I even talk about it?
Do you have to...
Enough, shut up.
It's about to be New Year.
Come, have a toast.
Come on.
In 2014,
a lot has happened to all of us.
Let's forget
all the bad things,
and keep up with
all the good things.
I hope all of us can
get a step closer to our dreams.
Come on, cheers, cheers!
Friends.
2014 is coming to an end.
Let's welcome 2015 together!
The countdown starts now.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Happy New Year!
It's so beautiful!
Cheers.
Happy New Year.
Cheers!
Cheers to our friendship!
Happy New Year!
Come on!
This place is really nice.
What's wrong?
Is she drunk after only one drink?
Maybe she drank it too fast?
Did she have a drink prior?
203's delivery riders all obey Chief Shao's management.
We also think highly of him.
But...
looking at our commission for the past few months,
we have some complaints
about the current plans.
You think the commission is too low, right?
Indeed.
Chief Shao insists that
every delivery rider of 203
take no more than
30 orders a day.
But
in other areas,
the riders take at least over 40 orders a day.
Last month's champion station, 201,
the riders there took 48 orders a day.
We delivery riders also compare within each other.
As time goes by,
it's inevitable that we feel frustrated.
I see.
Keep following Xingchi's orders at work
for the time being.
You can go now.
Mr. Xie.
Go ahead.
Fenghua seems to be
in poor physical condition lately.
What's wrong with her?
She looks very pale recently.
My mom and my wife both saw her vomiting in secret.
At first,
we thought she was pregnant.
Don't talk nonsense.
When I changed her pillow cover,
I found that she lost a lot of hair.
And there was blood on her toothbrush.
These are all symptoms of a weakened immune system.
Got it. Go.
You already had symptoms.
Why did it take you more than half a year to come?
Besides dizziness,
I just have a headache from time to time.
There are no other symptoms.
Have you been vomiting?
Yes.
Occasionally.
Do you feel
your eyesight has declined?
A bit, I think.
But everyone's on their phones nowadays.
It's normal to see things a little blurry, isn't it?
I suggest
you do
a thorough brain examination.
Really?
Is it that serious?
I can't...
give you a definitive diagnosis.
You're still young.
Go get examined,
and we'll talk after the result comes out.
All right?
Chen Xiaoyu, Room 3.
I can go by myself this time.
Okay.
I'll wait for you outside.
Guo Jianshe, Room 6.
Coming.
Xia Fenghua, Examination Room 2.
What's up with you?
I'm sorry.